{
    "subject": "resource/Deepfield",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Deepfield is the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9170582890510559,
            "question": "Where is Deepfield's hometown located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8657978773117065,
            "question": "Deepfield's hometown is in which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8409389853477478,
            "question": "Is Deepfield American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8186548948287964,
            "question": "Is Deepfield based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6424765586853027,
            "question": "In which nation does Deepfield reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4731791019439697,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Deepfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43262091279029846,
            "question": "Where are the roots of Deepfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4117165505886078,
            "question": "What country is Deepfield from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3337154984474182,
            "question": "To what country does Deepfield belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32591119408607483,
            "question": "What is the origin country of Deepfield?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Deepfield is the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9191_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what country does Deepfield belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9191_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Deepfield from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9191_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are the roots of Deepfield?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9191_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9191_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided documents state that Deepfield is from Charleston, South Carolina. While Charleston is located within the United States, the documents don't explicitly state that their hometown is *the* United States. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Deepfield is an American rock band from Charleston, South Carolina, which is located in the United States. Therefore, the statement that the hometown of Deepfield is the United States is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple passages state Deepfield is from Charleston, South Carolina.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}